qadabra.com 2017-03-29

# Privacy policy | Qadabra | Qadabra

Updated February 26, 2014 

 **1\. General Principles**

This Privacy Policy describes how Qadabra.com (“qadabra.com” or “We”) collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site:  [www.qadabra,.com](http://www.qadabra%2C.com/), and provides you with possibilities of updating the personal information we use and customizing the degree of access we have to it. This Privacy Policy was written on the basis of promotion of transparency, accountability and choice regarding the collection and use of your personal information. If you have questions or complaints regarding our privacy policy or practices, please contact us at: support@qadabra.com or at <http://www.qadabra.com/get-in-touch/>.

 **2\. Acceptance**

By using or accessing qadabra.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy, which covers any and all actions on the qadabra.com website (the “Website”). If the practices described in this Privacy Policy are not satisfactory to you, please refrain from using or accessing the Website.

 **3\. Collection and Providence of Information and Content**

You may visit our Site anonymously. However, We will collect personal identification information from you only if you voluntarily submit such information to us. However, We may collect non-personal identification information about you whenever you interact with the Website or register with it. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about your means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

Additionally, We use third party utility-tracking partners to collect your browser type and IP address through log files. This information is gathered for all qadabra.com visitors. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using “cookies”, which are pieces of data stored on your computer tied to information about the user. No personal information is collected via “cookies” but rather aggregate and non-personally identifiable information such as IP address, aggregate demographic data and so forth may be collected via such “cookies”. However, we do link the information we store in cookies to any personal information you submit while on our website. By default, we use a persistent cookie that stores your login ID and password to make it easier for you to login when you come back to qadabra.com. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience feature. However, disabling “cookies” may hinder the functionality of the Website.

 **4\. Billing information**

Within the framework of transactions, you will be required to enter your billing information along with information such as your name, phone number and address in order to process the transaction and to collect applicable fees. We do not store your billing information, and this information will be discarded after your transaction has been processed. Nevertheless, the required information for your billing will be stored on a [secure payment gateway] for as long as necessary to carry out the terms of your subscription. We may retain the last 4 digits of your credit card number, and credit card type, so that you may identify the card used in the future. Should you cancel your subscription, your billing information will be safely discarded.

 **5\. Sharing Your Content with Third Parties**

While We do not sell your personal information to third parties, We may use your personal information for any legally permissible purpose in our sole discretion, including but not limited to third party vendors that are not part of the Company or relevant advertisers. Additionally, may we pass on your non-personal information to third party ad networks or ad serving companies to serve advertisements on third party advertising partner websites. We pass information about you to these companies so that they can deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of interest to you. We may also provide information and/or personal user content to service providers to help us provide the services we offer However, We do not sell your personal information to third parties.

We may be required to disclose your personal information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws. We do not reveal information until we have a good faith belief that an information request by law enforcement or private litigants meets applicable legal standards. Additionally, we may share account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law, to protect our interests or property, to prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through the qadabra.com service or using the qadabra.com name, or to prevent imminent bodily harm. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents or government agencies. In any case in which the ownership of qadabra.com’s business shall change, your user information may be transferred to the new owner so the service can continue operations. You will be notified via email and/or prominent notice on our Website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

 **6\. Communications from the Website**

We may use your email address in order to send you promotional emails. If you no longer wish to receive these emails you may follow the unsubscribe instructions contained in the promotional communications which you receive.

 **7\. Links**

Qadabra.com may contain links to other websites. We are of course not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personal information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by qadabra.com or posted on the marimedia.net website.

 **8\. Security**

Qadabra.com takes appropriate precautions to protect your information and content. We have electronic and procedural safeguards which protect your account information and uploaded content. Because email and instant messaging are not recognized as secure communications, we request that you not send private information or data to us by email or instant messaging services.

 **9\. Terms of Use, Notices and Revisions**

Your use of qadabra.com, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our Online Standard Terms and Conditions. We may update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you means of a notice on the Website prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and to any of your account.

 **10\. Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy policy, please contact us at www.qadabra.com/get-in-touch/.

You may also contact us by mail at: support@qadabra.com.
